Billy, your mother's my best friend.
We're married.
That makes me your stepfather.
That makes you my responsibility.
If you love my mom so much, then you
should love me just as much, right?
Because I'm just like her.
Employee termination of services?
That means he's been lying about where
he's been going.
He hasn't been going to work.
Well done.
We're happy we've been going through.
He had been my father's best friend for
years.
Uncle Joe, as he called himself, had
watched me grow up and I was his princess.
But once I termed 18, something changed
about Joe.
His fondness for me turned into an
obsession.
So he came up with a plan to get me alone.
I'm going to put it inside you now,
Princess.
Just get it.
I made it up.
Dear mother, my dad.
It's Billy.
I need you to come to the kitchen right
now.
Now, Billy.
Coming, Dad.
So, you got my little notes in it?
Put some causal.
I'm wearing my pajamas.
What are you talking about?
What I'm talking about is this is this
isn't appropriate.
You can't go around the house dressed like
this.
What are you talking about?
These are my pajamas.
I'm 18.
I can wear whatever I want.
And you know that I've been wearing a t-shirt
and panties to bed my entire life now.
Look, you're not a little girl anymore.
You need to start dressing appropriately.
That's not appropriate.
This.
Give me this.
This is not appropriate.
This.
How is this appropriate?
I hope you like how my pussy smells,
Dad.
Yeah, yeah.
I know what it says, Billy.
This has to stop.
That's not clean.
Billy, pay attention to that.
Thank you.
Listen,
your mother is my best friend.
Okay, we're married now.
That makes me your stepfather.
That makes you my responsibility.
Do you have any idea how hard it was to
find someone like your mom?
How special both you guys are to me?
Well, yeah, I'm sure.
If you love my mom so much, then you
should love me just as much, right?
Because I mean, I look just like her.
And I'm, you know, younger, firmer, more
supple skin, tighter, probably more wet.
Just kidding.
Yes, I do love you, but not in that way.
Okay?
No, no.
Billy, stop.
Just... this has to.
You need to... What are you going to do
about it?
I don't know.
Maybe I was thinking
maybe we could... maybe
we could see a counselor
and work through this.
Because you guys are important.
I want this to work.
So me and you and your
mom, we could sit down and
have a professional
help us work through this.
And this is funny, do you think this is
funny?
Of her professional.
You think this is funny?
Yeah.
How was this funny?
I do, because why would
my mother ever believe
what you say over her
own daughter's words?
I mean, I could just say that you molested
me in my whole life.
Maybe that's fine.
I'm so fucked.
Because she fucking loves me one, two,
don't you ever, ever threaten me again.
Clean this up.
Put some clothes on.
I'm late for work.
And
I take a couple of
pictures for a little
present since she wants
to slam my muck around.
That way, in case mom sees it,
she sees it right now.
I wonder what daddy would think about
this.
I put her on my neck and it children me.
It's all like that.
I wonder if I will rub it off over my
body.
If my mom will be able to smell my flowery
person.
I need this one.
Now it's definitely going to smell like
me.
Her face will be right here.
Good job, Billy.
See, I did that.
And I did that.
I always kind of do that.
This isn't a bookmark.
Therefore, we regret to inform you on
behalf of the management that your
services have been terminated with
immediate effect.
Employee termination of services?
Wait a minute.
This is for me.
That was like four months ago.
Wait a minute.
That means he's been lying about where
he's been going.
He hasn't been going to work.
Well done.
We're happy been going.
I don't need to give mommy a dearest to
call.
Probably won't make up because she's
always busy but...
Hi, mom.
It's your favorite daughter, Billy.
I just wanted to let you know that you can
go ahead and attend that reading that you
had wanted to go to.
I finished up at school early and I can
take care of everything at home.
I know how to meet dinner.
So yeah, I've got it and I just wanted to
let you know that everything's all great
and I'll see you later.
I hope you have fun.
I love you, mom.
Bye.
Well, well, well, Mr. Fox.
Cindy?
Hello?
Billy?
Guys, I'm back from work.
Hi, daddy.
What are you doing making in my bed?
Is that my tie?
Maybe.
Okay, look.
Your mom's going to be home in a few
minutes.
We talked about this morning.
So I need you to, first of all,
give me my damn tie back because your mom
gave that to me for our engagement
present.
Oh, she gave this to for an engagement
present?
Yes.
Really?
That's funny because it was like all the
way in my car today.
Like I shoved it all the way in.
Okay, great.
Whatever.
So put your clothes on.
Get the hell out of there.
But the funny thing is mom isn't going to
be home anytime soon.
You see, I called and I told her that you
and I...
Well, we have some things we need to discuss
and we really needed some a lot of time.
Okay, great.
We can talk.
We can talk with your
clothes on out here because
there's nothing we
need to discuss right here.
But I don't want that.
Okay, yeah.
Look, great.
So your mom's going to be home in a couple
of minutes.
I need you to get your clothes on and get
out.
Now, let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Mom isn't going to be home anytime soon.
I took care of that already.
Yeah, she's always home the same time
every day like clockwork.
Okay, so you really need to come on.
Let's go.
Exactly.
And, you know, I called
her and I told her that
you and I had, you know,
some things to discuss.
And we really needed some a lot of time.
Okay, great.
We can talk.
We can talk with your clothes on
out here because there's nothing
we need to discuss right here
in my bedroom with you naked.
Oh, really?
Well, this little TV right here.
Where did you get this?
I found it.
You left it out.
You should have done that.
Okay, look.
Speechless?
I bet.
What have you been doing all day,
dad?
Huh?
I didn't start as I didn't want to stress
her out over this.
Why lie?
Oh, you didn't want to stress her out.
She's your best friend.
She's my best friend.
You've been searching for this all your
life, right, dad?
And it's been so many years.
What have you been working on,
huh?
When you grab your fucking
briefcase and you storm
out of the door and you're
about to give up on me?
What are you working on?
Are you working on the neighbor's pussy
down the street?
Darla?
I think she's fans to do for quite some
time.
Oh, yeah.
Did you want to hit me, dad?
Do you want to punch me?
Does this make you angry?
Oh, did I make you angry?
Are you doing this?
Does this make you hard?
No.
Stop.
Haven't you always
wondered what it would be
like to be balls deep
in your stepdaughters?
18-year-old pussy?
Don't you wonder how tight it is?
Billy, all I've wondered what
it would be like is to have a
normal household where we
can be happy together as a family.
That's all I want.
And you just act like a normal human being
first.
The perfect little American dream family.
Well, dad, that can't happen if you're a
fucking liar, huh?
No, panic, cause I mean, listen,
let me tell you how we can fix things.
Right now at this, at this juncture,
it's your fucked one way or another,
because I have a friend who, when mommy
dearest is laying in bed with you at
night, getting ready to set her alarm for
work the next day, because you guys always
run on fucking schedule, cause you're just
so fucking perfect, right?
She'll get the text with the termination
letter and everything.
Wait, wait, wait, someone else knows about
this.
You told someone else about this.
So this, this is never going to end.
You're just going to keep on this forever,
right?
Is that, what do you want?
Do you, do you want money?
Do you want a car?
A vacation for your
silly friends that like,
Coachella, whatever the hell
you guys go on the desert?
What do you, what do you want?
One, Coachella, three.
All three.
And two, I don't want a car, and I don't
want money.
I want you to fuck me first, daddy.
Yeah, I'll just shove your back off the
deep in my tight little pussy.
I hate you.
I hate nothing.
This is what you want, huh?
Come here.
Enough of this nonsense.
Will this make you stop, huh?
Will this make you stop?
Huh?
It's got potential.
Come on, let's see if this is a tie with
the rest of the family.
I really want to know.
That's it.
Good girl.
Such a bad girl.
You want to stick your cock in place with
your balls, daddy?
Your mom uses both hands.
Show me you can do it better than you want
to do it.
What does that feel good?
That's pretty good.
You're watching all your guys' home
videos.
You're careful it's locked down.
My thumb's cute.
Your mom's a little bit better.
You have been cheating on mom.
Like fathers.
Right in the head.
What am I supposed to do now?
空...
空... 空...
Colour on your own secret... It's
not cheating with the neighbor.
If your mom is there, too.
Right, fucking snot.
You want to act like an adult?
My pussy looks like my mom's pussy.
Stop talking about your mother.
That's what you want, right, look, what
you found the size to be about, huh?
Did mom suck your dick so hard she gets
tears on her eyes?
I'm talking about your mom.
You finally got me here and now you're
talking about her mom.
Well, I wish you'd joke on your cock like
this.
Mom, eat yours.
Mom, don't eat this.
No, no, no, no, no.
Um...
I'll get you some more.
Let's go see daddy.
Yeah, get some of this too.
It tastes gypsy and thick.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's nice look.
It's a fucking nasty thing.
Ah, okay.
I don't have yet, daddy.
You know what I always fantasize?
If you came to me like you do.
Stop it now.
Stop.
Pull the dick back into your mouth and
stop it.
Do you want to be on my little pussy bear
back?
Just put your mommy dearest.
Shut up.
You want to do a grown-up thing,
huh?
Come here, I've got something grown up for
you.
You can get on this.
You can get on your stuff.
You're finally going to fuck me first,
daddy.
Is this between you?
Yes, it's between you and I.
I want to fuck my stuff, dad.
Tell me you want your stuff, dad.
It's cock.
Oh, I'm sorry, my friend.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
Oh, you're not going to fuck me.
Do you like it?
Very nice.
Nazly, you have not caught my head?
I'm fucking pussy.
Yeah, damn, I'm fucking pussy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
I want to see how I put my back in a
little surface.
Yeah.
Oh, you're fucking telling me guys.
Is this like a normal?
No, it's not like a normal.
Yes, dear, fucking dirty.
We be a little girl.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, fucking hard and
dirty.
Yeah!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, don't come.
It's so tight for you.
It's a tight on my eyes.
Not yet.
Oh.
It's... It's a tight.
It's... It's...
We like it so much.
We are back.
Let's do this.
Are you... oh!
You tie mom up like this?
It is a Rolav crush.
attack me.
You fucking bloge.
He tied mom up like a's daddy,
it is your Ro v too much.
Can I tie her up like this?
You see how flexible you are?
Well, you didn't pay for those nasty
classes for nothing, Daddy.
This is how we're tying her up.
Oh, you have tie her up like this?
Yeah, in the back of me like how you put
them on.
This is how you tie mom up in the back of
it.
Yep, just like that.
Oh, just like that?
Oh, yes, fuck me, Daddy.
Fuck me like how you fuck mom.
Yeah, just like that.
Yeah, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I want you to break my little pussy,
Daddy.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Thank you, the bad little girl.
You guys told me to do.
I told you what to do.
Yeah.
But when it be a daddy, when I could be
the girl, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, yes, fuck me like that.
When you go on mom to get that letter,
don't do it.
This is what I think about doing that.
Okay, I want you to make me angry.
Make me want to break my little pussy.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
What are you doing, Daddy, huh?
Fuck me like how you fuck me now.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Fuck me hard.
Oh, yes, we said you fucking hated me.
Fuck me like you fucking hated me.
Oh, yes, you fucking mom.
This is all tired of like this.
I'm not for this.
Come here.
I know you always thought about it.
I want you to stick it in like you always
thought about it.
Oh, yes, just like that.
Just like that.
And like this.
Fuck!
Oh, yes, yes.
You're like having your hands up on my
toes.
Fuck me.
And watch Daddy dick inside your pussy.
Watch the Daddy dick in your pussy.
You're like having your mom's pussy.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, Daddy.
Fuck my pussy.
Fuck me mom.
Show me like how you joke mom.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, oh, yes, yes.
Oh, you are not my mom.
Oh, oh, oh, no, no.
Oh, oh, no, no, no, no.
Are you doing it for my pussy?
Yes, like you do mom.
I know you've wanted it as much as I have.
You've got about it.
Yes, you have.
You're not going to show the fuck off.
You fucking won't make enough of a turn.
Maybe you had more.
And he's got to tell the truth.
Oh, you're fucking come on, we got the
gun, daddy.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, I'm fucking cut.
Is that all you fucking got?
What the fuck?
Oh, fuck!
I want to feel it in my cervix.
I don't really feel the world in my pussy.
I feel all of your stuff on your pussy.
Oh, I'm so hard.
I'm just like I always imagined in my
dreams.
Is this what you wanted?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I don't know.
I bet you taught yourself thinking about
your step-dad's dick, and you don't you?
Yes, step-dad's dick.
You taught too much.
Come here.
What are you going to do, bud?
That's what you're going to do.
Come here.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm talking too much shit now.
How are you?
Yeah, you can't fool my pussy.
I'm gonna put it in my mouth.
I want to taste my juices.
Oh, come on.
Oh, you already fucked me like how you
fucked me.
I fucked you up.
I said, I mean, you're gonna come at me
harder.
You're fired like hell.
You're a fucking lash чα raised.
Don't you want me to cut you up?
You're going to cut me up today.
I'm not gonna come here, you weird stuff,
dog.
I'm not gonna come here.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't have a pussy...
Yes, yes, my foot.
Would you fucking fill it up with calm?
Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes.
Where?
Come in me.
No.
I want you fucking come in me.
I want my daddy to come in me.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Come in me.
No.
I want you fucking come in me.
Oh, you just show me.
You thought that you are your fucking mom?
And you stole my shadow under the door?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you going to come in me?
Stop daughter.
The perfect American family, right?
Sharing is caring, right, dad?
It's not going to fucking talk me.
Oh, yes, yes.
You're not going to happen.
It's not going to happen.
Oh, I want you to come in me, daddy.
Yes, oh, yes, yes, yes, fuck me with that.
A hard cock.
Oh, so my pussy up like you do mom.
Oh, God, it's so hard.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I want you to come in me.
Yes, yes, so I want you to come in me.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, please come.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I want you to come in me.
Please come in me.
Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm completely out of breath...
One of my tight little pussy.
And some of your balls while you fuck me.
Does mom do this to you?
Huh?
Oh, and yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I've always wanted to feel you're coming
to me.
Oh, I thought about you so well,
buddy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, please give me what I want.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, come on my tight little fucking pussy.
Yes.
Oh, yes, come in.
Oh, my God.
Oh, don't say that.
No,
you just came in your 18 year old
daughter.
Look at my little siblings.
Oh, just shut up, you're so small.
Oh, you came in my tight little 18 year
old pussy.
Okay, look, that's enough.
That's enough.
Oh, look, it's like daycare down there.
Stop it.
Honey, mom?
John?
I... I... I... I... I... I... I... I...
I... I... I... I... I... I... I... I... I...
I... He had been my father's best
friend for years since they were boys.
Best man on my parents' wedding?
There in the waiting room the day I was
born.
Prisons at every birthday party.
Uncle Joe, as he called himself, had
watched me grow up, And I was his princess.
The niece he never had.
But once I turned 18, something changed
about Joe.
His fondness for me turned into an
obsession.
Every time he was over at the house,
he would become distracted by my body.
And how much he liked to take advantage of
it.
But he knew he couldn't do anything while
my dad was around.
So, he came up with a plan to get me
alone.
Wow, Uncle Joe, this place is so nice!
It's way better than your last day.
Check out the views.
Wow, this view is incredible.
I wish we lived here.
You got to see the amenities.
What amenities?
The pool.
You have a pool?
Did you bring your suit?
Oh my God, Uncle Joe, I'm so sorry.
Uncle Joe?
Okay.
Did you happen to see where I put my bag?
No, I haven't seen it.
Look at you.
You're freezing.
Put that one.
I'm really excited about this weekend.
I have an incredible height plan for us.
I believe it's 13, maybe 14,000 feet
straight up.
Wow.
So, it's going to take us a while to get
to the top.
But the view is absolutely worth it.
I better do that.
And if we're lucky, maybe we'll see some
hawks.
And if we're super lucky, maybe even a
ball legal.
You know what?
What's that?
It's getting late.
You should probably get some rest.
It's getting ready for bed.
What's the matter?
You don't think it's weird, do you?
Where am I sleeping?
Well, right here.
I figure we're both adults.
You are 18 now.
What?
There's nothing weird about two adults
sharing the bed.
Come on now.
Climb in because you're going to need your
rest for tomorrow.
We got a big dad.
Uncle Joe?
I'm going to put it inside you now,
Princess.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Is
that all the way in here?
Is that okay?
Yes.
You're such a big brother.
Oh my god.
Is that okay?
I've been wanting to make you feel good
for so long.
How do you?
I knew I could help you.
You've always been my little princess.
Well, I just want to make you feel good.
I see those pretty little eyes.
Good girl.
Oh my god, Uncle Joe.
Oh my god.
You feel even better than I think.
I see your pretty little mommy.
Look at you.
You're not a little girl, aren't you?
You know how much I love you?
You've always been very special to me.
Uncle Joe, how much do you like him?
I hope so.
Use your hand to me.
Like that?
Good girl.
Oh, just like that.
You're doing great, sweetheart.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm finished.
I'm done.
Oh, you're so good.
That's
it.
Oh, fuck yes.
That's it.
You're natural.
It's so good.
Can you feel that cog right here?
You always wear my favorite jeans.
Yeah.
Stay with me, baby.
You're doing great.
Make Uncle Joe very happy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, you smell so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's so deep.
Oh, you smell so good.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's so deep.
Oh,
my God, yes, yes.
Good.
It looks so pretty.
Okay.
Here, in the middle.
That's it.
Oh, good girl.
Put your tongue out.
Yes...
Oh my god...
Oh my god... Oh
my god... Oh yes...
Oh my god... You have
all good job what he needs.
Oh my god... Oh yes... Yes...
Wait on the pillow if
you have to... Tuts in...
Yes... Yes...
Yes... Oh my god... Oh my god... Oh my
god... Oh my god... Oh my god... Oh my god...
Oh my god... Oh girl...
Oh my god... Oh my...
Oh my god, I'm so,
so, so, so deep.
Oh my... Oh my...
Oh my god!
Oh.
That's a crazy expression.
That's right.
You're ready.
Yes.
I just said I don't want to go to you.
Oh.
Yes.
So good.
Oh.
Yes.
I want you to sit down.
Sit down, I want you to sit down.
Show me what a big girl you are.
I'm going to...
I'm going to... I'm
going to... Oh my God...
Oh my God!
Ah!
Yes!
God!
That's it.
Fuck you.
Oh my God!
Yes!
Ah!
Oh my God!
Yes!
Oh God!
Oh my God!
Oh my god, ouch!
Yes!
Ah!
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Oh, my God, no...
Oh, my God...
Yes, yes...
Oh, fuck, that's a good call, yes...
I told you, my baby...
Oh, my God, I can't believe we're doing
this.
That's fine, you're an adult.
You feel good, right?
Is it make you happy?
Yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes...
So, you're special to you, isn't it?
Yes, yes... Yes, yes.
..
Oh, my God, I feel so good.
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God.
..
Oh, fuck...
Just squeeze that finger.
Oh, my God.
..
Oh, my God...
Do you want it?
Yes... Tell me what... I want
it to come on, go check.
You know... I suppose you're
going to make me come.
Yes...
Oh, fuck...
Oh, fuck.
..
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God, yes... Oh,
my God... Oh, my God.
..
Oh, my God...
Oh, yeah... Oh, my God.
..
Oh, yes...
Oh, yeah... Oh, fuck...
Oh, my God... Oh, I
love you, Frances.
I love you too, Uncle Joe.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Oh, my God.
..